<rss version="0.91">
<channel>
<item>
<title>The Secret Garden of My nDreams</title>
<description>by Phoenix, HSM team writer

(This article was first published in Homestation Magazine July 6th, 2014)

Twilight falls with muted colors around the space. Ivy and flowers grace the terracotta; blue tiles and Persian rug covered walls. Scattered about the wooden floors are more of these rugs, along with overstuffed cushions in rich jewel and earthen tones. Fairy lights are strung all around the cathedral-esque floor plan; a Portico overlooking a tranquil night scene, a kind of narthex with circular endings studded with cushions for comfort, Nave and aisles on either side enclosing ancient trees that could have sprung directly from the space where they stand.

<img src="http://scee-home.playstation.net/e.home/hosted/CommercePoints/Thumbnails/garden1SGP.dds"/>
A Bema follows where a clear spring with a mosaic fountain murmuring with mellifluous music is tucked; surrounded by rocks and filled with lotus blossoms. And, finally, in an altar-like position at the head of the floor plan is a curtained area with more cushions atop an enormous rounded floor cushion. Above your head, the sky is visible through the cathedral canopy-like roof.

The perfect design for this halcyon garden retreat.

<img src="http://scee-home.playstation.net/e.home/hosted/CommercePoints/Thumbnails/garden2SGP.dds"/>

This new space from nDreams so surprised me, that I wondered - why now? Why hadn’t this space been here in Home before now, at the end of my time here? There is such a feeling of sanctuary and completion to it. A feeling of rest and relaxation came over me such that I envied my avatar's surrounding. I could see it as an escape from reality. An escape from the long days of traffic jams, summer's sweltering heat, the noise and chatter of the market and every other little thing that has grown into a constant gnat in one's ear.  It has character, personality, substance, a well-executed design, and perfect placement of the elements that make up the space. The light in the space is balanced well with the darkened areas. A free, relaxed BoHo feel, almost. It is realistic and fantastical at once.

After so many weeks away from Home, I actually felt like this place should be an escape. Had I a wish list for a getaway in the real world,it would be the exact specifications and details of nDreams' Secret Party Garden. nDreams created the secret garden in my dreams.
<img src="http://scee-home.playstation.net/e.home/hosted/CommercePoints/Thumbnails/garden4SGP.dds"/>
As Home draws closer to a close, I've been able to spend less and less time here. It would appear the universe has contrived to lessen my free time, perhaps to make Home's inevitable disappearance less noticeable to me. Whatever the reason, I have spent little time of late in this virtual world, so I had not seen or visited some of the newer spaces, whereas before I made it my habit to do so. I searched out every little gem and nugget Home had to offer. I enjoy the meta home décor game/sideline in Home.

I admit to being a fan of the spaces that have lots of personality and character. Those spaces that have dynamic environments, whether it is sound or movement, are among my favorite properties. Spaces like the Uncharted apartment, with the traffic sounds and moving vehicles, Assassin's Creed with its busy Venetian city sounds, the Sunset Yacht, with the active marine life and sailing motion all pull me into their immersion experience. These spaces with their burned-in love were the beginning of Home's appeal for me. They offer the little something extra that made them like a home away from home. The detailing in these spaces have in my opinion more over some others, carved wood panels, brocade wallpaper, old air conditioners that vibrate and choke to continue working (little things) carry a lot of character.

When it came to decorating I was always interested in adding my own character to a space. Spaces that have a great deal of burn-in could be a turn off to me, no matter how big the space. I have recently acquired some of the larger personal spaces to decorate and post to my page. In my collection, however, I have only two from nDreams. One I purchased; the other was free. I liked some of their spaces, but after visiting them was not impressed enough to purchase them.
<img src="http://scee-home.playstation.net/e.home/hosted/CommercePoints/Thumbnails/garden5SGP.dds"/>

Last night I came across the Secret Garden space.

To this space I have only added a jukebox from LOOT, which I have set to calming atmospheric sounds. It almost felt like a sacrilege to add more. The Secret Garden space stands on its own as one I will remember fondly as Home fades. To answer my own question (as to why now), perhaps because it is time; time for a space of this calibre. There is nothing I could think of, with all the items I have amassed, which adds to this space.

I typically look at nDreams estates as a blank slate upon which to create. In this case, the slate is full, rendered in an enchanting level of detail. Highly recommended.

<img src="http://scee-home.playstation.net/e.home/hosted/CommercePoints/Thumbnails/phoenixstorm21.dds"/>

</description>

</item>
</channel>
</rss> 